{
    "subject": "resource/Martin_J._Taylor",
    "predicate": "property/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/Pembroke_College,_Oxford",
    "human_readable": "Martin J. Taylor attended Pembroke College, Oxford.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9802649021148682,
            "question": "Did Martin J. Taylor attend Pembroke College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9335325956344604,
            "question": "Was Martin J. Taylor a student at Oxford?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8844778537750244,
            "question": "Where did Martin J. Taylor attend college?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8748984932899475,
            "question": "What college is Martin J. Taylor known to have attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8631830811500549,
            "question": "What is the name of the college Martin J. Taylor attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7955564856529236,
            "question": "What college was Martin J. Taylor associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7805860638618469,
            "question": "Name the university Martin J. Taylor studied at."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7321811318397522,
            "question": "At what institution did Martin J. Taylor pursue his education?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6919031739234924,
            "question": "In which university did Martin J. Taylor study?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6738119125366211,
            "question": "To which institution did Martin J. Taylor go to for his studies?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Martin J. Taylor attended Pembroke College, Oxford.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4378_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which university did Martin J. Taylor study?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4378_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=At what institution did Martin J. Taylor pursue his education?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4378_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the university Martin J. Taylor studied at.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4378_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4378_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4378_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4378_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4378_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4378_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4378_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4378_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4378_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4378_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4378_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text mentions that Martin J. Taylor attended Pembroke College, **Oxford**, not Pembroke College, Cambridge.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "The triple to evaluate is \"Martin J. Taylor attended Pembroke College, Oxford\". \n\nGiven the context information and without prior knowledge:\n\n* The first two documents mention a person named Martin J. Taylor, but they do not provide any information about his educational background or attendance at Pembroke College, Oxford.\n* The other documents are unrelated to Martin J. Taylor.\n \nTherefore, based on the available information in the documents provided, it is not possible to determine whether Martin J. Taylor attended Pembroke College, Oxford.\n\nThe answer should be:\n\n`{'output': 'no'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe context information provided mentions James Arthur Taylor as having studied at Pembroke College, Oxford. While the name \"Taylor\" in the query does not directly match \"James Arthur,\" it is reasonable to infer that the documents are discussing James Arthur Taylor based on the detailed academic and professional information given. Therefore, the statement that Martin J. Taylor attended Pembroke College, Oxford, can be considered correct according to the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Martin J. Taylor attended Pembroke College, Oxford is incorrect as the context information provided indicates that he went to Pembroke College, Cambridge for his undergraduate studies, not Oxford.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text explicitly states that Martin J. Taylor gained a first class degree from Pembroke College, Oxford in 1973.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The text mentions two individuals named Taylor with similar information, one of them being Martin J. Taylor who attended Pembroke College, Oxford, but the same name and institution are also mentioned for a second person. However, I see that the context actually refers to Pembroke College, Cambridge, not Oxford, in sections 5 and 6.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}